Guide to the Brooklyn letterhead collection BCMS.0008
Brooklyn Collection
- Young & Smylie, 1902
  Licorice maker. Lorimer and Bayard Streets
- Zeh, Philip (& Son) / Zeh & Campbell, 1864, 1866, 1871, 1886
  Florists. Cor. 23rd St. and 5th Ave. [Greenwood]
- Zollinger, E., 1896
  Confectioner. 85 Fulton Street
- Zolzer, Chas F., 1888
  Plumber. 207 Court Street
- Zuckerkandel, Leon, 1944
  Stationer and toys. 2505 Mermaid Avenue
- Zwingli, Arnold, 1891
  19 Humboldt Street